{
    "subject": "resource/VH1",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "VH1",
    "human_readable": "VH1's name is VH1.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7508774995803833,
            "question": "Is VH1 known for any specific shows or programming?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6774108409881592,
            "question": "Who owns VH1?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6640892624855042,
            "question": "Is VH1 available internationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.631161630153656,
            "question": "When was VH1 founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5336052775382996,
            "question": "Is VH1 a popular music channel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.496430903673172,
            "question": "What kind of music does VH1 typically feature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4782622456550598,
            "question": "Has VH1 won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46981632709503174,
            "question": "What is the target audience for VH1?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40521320700645447,
            "question": "Does VH1 play music videos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08939364552497864,
            "question": "What is the name of the music television channel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=VH1's name is VH1.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4355_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does VH1 play music videos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4355_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the target audience for VH1?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4355_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has VH1 won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4355_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4355_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context confirms that VH1 (VH1) has the name as stated, even though it also mentions the stylized version as Vl+1. The confirmation of its full name being VH1 aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}